dailybreak.com 2012-12-05

# Dailybreak - Bite-Sized Contests About Stuff You Love

Dailybreak, Inc. (“Dailybreak,” “we,” “us,” “our”) provides its services (described below) to you through its website located at www.dailybreak.com (the “Web site”) and through its mobile applications and related services (collectively, such services, including any new features and applications, and the Web site, the “Service(s)”), subject to the following Privacy Policy (as amended from time to time, this “Policy”). By accessing or using the Services or by registering as a member of the Services, you consent to the collection and use of your Personal Data (defined below) as described in this Policy. This Policy applies to all users of the Servcies, including users who are also registered members. If you are unwilling to consent to our collection and use of your Personal Data as described in this Policy or to accept the terms in the Terms of Use that apply to use of the Services, you should not use the Services.

Collection and Use of Personal Data

Your privacy is important to Dailybreak. We at times collect, retain and utilize Personal Data about you to operate the Servcies and our business and to notify you of services and other opportunities offered by Dailybreak or its partners. The term "Personal Data" means data that can reasonably be used to identify you that Dailybreak obtains about you, including your name, telephone number, physical address and email address. We recognize and respect your privacy concerns about this information. We obtain Personal Data in a variety of ways (for example, as provided by you when you register to use the Services, or from your other transactions or experiences with Dailybreak or its affiliates, including comments and information that you submit when utilizing the "social networking" aspects of the Services)

We may send promotional email messages to you on behalf of third parties. We do not share your Personal Data with such third parties, and you have the opportunity to opt out of such promotional messages by "unsubscribing".

You do not have to sign-up to use the Services. However, in order to customize your page and take full advantage of the Services features, you do have to sign-up. If you sign onto the Services using your account with a social networking platform (e.g., Facebook) and you agree to allow Dailybreak to access your account information with such social networking platform, including your name, email address, profile picture, gender, "networks", user ID (but not your password), list of friends, and "any other information I've shared with everyone", Dailybreak may collect and use such information to make your use of the Services richer and more personalized, and as described in this Policy. If you allow Dailybreak access to such data, Dailybreak may access that data at any time, including when you are not using the Services. However, please remember that the manner in which social networking platforms use, store and disclose your information is governed by the policies of such third parties, and Dailybreak shall have no liability or responsibility for the privacy practices or other actions of any social networking platform that may be enabled on or within the Service. You may also have the option of posting your activities within the Services to third party social networking platforms when you access and use content and features through the Services (for example, you may post to Facebook that you entered or won a promotion on the Services); you acknowledge that if you choose to use this feature, your friends, followers and subscribers on any social networking platforms you have enabled will be able to view such activity.

Log Files; Aggregated Personal Data

As is true of most websites and mobile applications, Dailybreak may gather certain information automatically through the Services and store it in log files. This information, which does not identify you, includes Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We may use this information to track user demographics, user habits and improve the functionality of the Services as a result of our observations, and to conduct research and analyses on an aggregate basis. Dailybreak may share this aggregate data with its affiliates, agents and business partners, and may also disclose aggregated user statistics in order to describe its Services to current and prospective business partners, and to other third parties for other lawful purposes.

Dailybreak uses cookies to track non-personally identifiable information about visitors to the Services in the aggregate so that Dailybreak can learn which advertisements and Services features bring Internet users to the Services, analyze trends, administer the Services, track users’ movements around the site, and gather demographic information about its user base as a whole. Cookies are small data files that a website can place on a user’s computer to allow the website to store and retrieve data about that particular user so that the Services can provide or perform a variety of tasks and functions. Dailybreak does not link the information it stores in cookies to any of your Personal Data.

Spotlight Tags

Dailybreak may also use spotlight tags, which are transparent GIF files embedded in the Services, to help manage and track the effectiveness of online advertising. Spotlight tags enable the recognition of a unique cookie on your web browser, which in turn enables us to learn which advertisements bring users to the Services. The cookie would be placed by us, or by another advertiser who works with us. The information that we may collect via spotlight tags and share is anonymous and not personally identifiable.

Geo-Location Information

Our Services may collect and use your location information (for example, by using the GPS on your mobile device) to provide certain functionality of our Services. If you choose to enable our location features, your location information may be publicly displayed within the Services. Please keep in mind that other users can see this information about you, and they may use it or disclose it to other individuals or entities outside of our control and without your knowledge. Your location information may be subject to abuse, misuse, and monitoring by others, so please be careful if you choose to enable location functionality. We may also use your location information in an aggregate way, as described above in the “Aggregated Personal Data” section above.

Disclosure of Information

Dailybreak encourages you to carefully choose the information you submit, post, or provide to others using the Services or Services features (e.g., comments, blogs, video chat sessions, mobile applications, promotion entries). Dailybreak is not responsible for disclosures made by you through the social networking features of the Services.

Except as indicated within this Policy, we will not sell, rent or transfer your Personal Data to or otherwise share your Personal Data with third parties. We may share or transfer your Personal Data as directed to do so by you (for example, in setting up a new account). We may transfer Personal Data to third party vendors who act for us for further processing in accordance with the purposes for which the data was originally collected or for purposes to which you have subsequently consented. For example, sometimes a third party vendor may have access to your Personal Data in order to support our information technology or help compile and manage the data. All Dailybreak vendors operate under federal and state laws regarding consumer privacy. Dailybreak is not responsible for the privacy policies and practices of third parties, however, including vendors and third party service providers.

We may also disclose Personal Data about you as required or permitted by law, including to comply with legal process (for example, we may disclose your information as necessary to comply with an authorized civil, criminal or regulatory investigation).

We may, in our sole discretion, share or transfer your Personal Data to protect the security or integrity of our databases or the Services, to protect our business or reputation, to take precautions against legal liability, in the event of a business transition (see below), to protect and defend our rights or property, for required institutional risk control, or for resolving disputes, inquiries or complaints with respect to your access and use of the Services. We may sell or transfer aggregate data that does not identify you.

Third Party Cookies

Notwithstanding any other provision in this policy, in visiting this site, a third-party advertiser (or its partners) may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. These cookies enable more customized ads, content or services to be provided to you. To trigger these cookies, we may pass an encrypted or "hashed" (non-human readable) identifier corresponding to your email address to a Web advertising partner, who may place a cookie on your computer. No personally identifiable information is on, or is connected to, these cookies. To opt-out of these cookies, please go to <http://www.privacychoice.org/companies> or <http://www.aboutads.info/choices>.

Personal Data Submitted by You for Review by other Users

You post User Submissions (as defined in and governed by the Dailybreak Terms of Use) on the Services at your own risk. We cannot control the actions of other users with whom you may choose to share your Personal Data. We cannot and do not guarantee that User Submissions you post or submit on or through the Services will not be viewed by unauthorized persons. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Services. You understand and acknowledge that, even after removal, copies of User Submissions may remain viewable in cached and archived pages or if other users have copied or stored your User Submissions.

Any improper collection or misuse of Personal Data provided on the Services is a violation of the Dailybreak Terms of Use and should be reported to [support@dailybreak.com](malito:support@dailybreak.com).

Links to Other Sites

You should know that while accessing and using the Services, you can be directed, through links, to other websites that are beyond Dailybreak’s control. Dailybreak is not responsible for the privacy practices and policies of such websites.

Maintenance of Accurate Information

We have established procedures to correct inaccurate information in a timely manner. If you have any reason to believe that Personal Data about you that is stored and maintained by us is incorrect, please contact us by email at: [support@dailybreak.com](malito:support@dailybreak.com).

Protection of Information

We strive to maintain the reliability, accuracy, completeness and currency of your Personal Data in our databases and to protect the privacy and security of our databases and the data we collect. Any Personal Data that you provide to us will be stored on our computer network servers. We maintain reasonable physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect the confidentiality of your Personal Data. The security measures in place on the Services and related computer systems aim to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of the information you provide to us. However, no Internet or email transmission is ever fully secure or error free. In particular, email sent to or from the Services may not be secure. Therefore, you should take special care in deciding what information you send to us via email. If you have any questions or concerns regarding the security of your information, please email us at [support@dailybreak.com](malito:support@dailybreak.com).

Business Transitions

In the event Dailybreak goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your Personal Data might be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via the Services of any such change in ownership or control of your Personal Data.

Changes in Dailybreak Privacy Policy

If we decide to change this Policy, we will post the changes on or through the Services and at other places we deem appropriate. We reserve the right to modify this Policy at any time, so please review it frequently.

Effective Date

This Policy is effective as of November 6, 2012.

Contact Us 

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding this Policy, please contact Dailybreak at: 

Dailybreak, Inc.,   
100 North Washington Street,   
Boston, MA 02114

By phone at (617) 451-1790

Or by e-mail at [support@dailybreak.com](mailto:support@dailybreak.com).
